popjustice.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy • Popjustice

We have definitely not copied this generic privacy statement from somewhere else.

Popjustice is committed to protecting your privacy online. We appreciate that you do not want any personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have. By accessing and continuing to use this website, you accept the terms of this privacy policy. Please note that we may update and amend the privacy policy from time to time and your are encouraged to check back from time to time. If you do not agree with any of our privacy policy then you should not use the website.

 **What data do we collect?**

So that we can provide a personalised service, we may, upon registration or at other times, ask you to submit personal information such as a name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You are under no obligation to provide such information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

 **How is the information used?**

Popjustice will use the information you provide to us to:

  * Monitor, develop and improve the website, services and your experience;
  * Assist in and administer the provision of services to you;
  * Process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by or about you;
  * Investigate any suspected breach of the Terms & Conditions or the breach of other terms otherwise relating to you and to monitor compliance including by way of checking postings or submissions to the website, and/or retaining forum or chat room exchanges and using keyword triggers to investigate usage that may be inappropriate.

Where and only where requested by you we will:

  * Send you and keep you updated with information by email, telephone (including SMS) or mail about existing and new services and special offers from us; and/or
  * Send you information by email, telephone or mail about related products or services of selected third parties that may be of interest to you.

You can tell us not to contact you or share the information with a third party either at initial registration or later through updates or amendments to your personal information. We may occasionally contact you about products and services we feel may be of interest to you. This will only come from us (or our agents) and only if you have indicated that you do not object to these offers.

 **With whom is the information shared?**

At times, Popjustice may enter into co-branding arrangements with other reputable organisations, with whom your personal information may be shared. You can, however, tell us not to do so at any time, by sending an e-mail message to privacy [at] popjustice [dot] com.

Popjustice may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to collecting the data or prior to transferring it.

Popjustice may disclose aggregate statistics about our site visitors, clients and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

Popjustice may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Popjustice, the site or its visitors.

This site contains links to other sites. Popjustice is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

 **Security**

Popjustice places a great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our clients. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of client data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised personnel have access to user information.  While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

 **Use of cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user’s computer, cookies do not personally identify users and passwords and credit card information are not stored in cookies.

We may use cookies to:

  * Identify who you are and to access your account information;
  * Estimate our audience size and patterns;
  * Control how often visitors see similar ads; and
  * Track preferences and to improve and update our website.

 **Where is the information stored?**

Information which you submit via this website is sent to a computer located in the United Kingdom. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and to other reputable third party organisations, which may be situated outside the European Economic Area.

In addition if you use our services while you are outside the EEA, your information may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with those services.

 **Keeping our records accurate**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible, but we depend on our users to update their personal information whenever necessary. You can review, change or delete the details you have supplied to us at any time by use of your profile on this site or by contacting us. If you have another query relating to your information, please contact us as set out below.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Popjustice and to the Popjustice privacy policy. If we change our privacy policy in any way, we will post these changes on this page.

Please e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about these policies to Peter Robinson at privacy [at] popjustice [dot] com.

Tell you what, if you think this page has been boring, wait until you see the[ T&Cs](http://www.popjustice.com/about/terms-and-conditions/ "Terms & Conditions").
